<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<add xmlns="http://lucene.apache.org/solr/4/document" xmlns:gmd="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmd" xmlns:gco="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gco" xmlns:solr="http://lucene.apache.org/solr/4/document">
  <doc>
    <field name="uuid">3f2f9cba-a35d-47de-b027-cd498383f8e8-28</field>
    <field name="dc_identifier_s">3f2f9cba-a35d-47de-b027-cd498383f8e8-28</field>
    <field name="dc_title_s">Floodplain 500y: County of Albemarle 2010 GIS Datasets (Datastack)</field>
    <field name="dc_description_s">This collection (stacked series) of datasets is provided to the UVA Library's Scholars' Lab by the office of Geographic Data Services (GDS) of the County of Albemarle, Virginia, USA. The data are managed and maintained by the GDS department which is a branch of the Department of Community Development, and are provided AS-IS with no guarantees as regards to their accuracy or temporal currency. The data pertains primarily to the infrastructure within the County of Albemarle as well as related natural features and emergency response information. *//* The temporal extent of the datasets in the datastack is generally current as of August 2010, but some datasets may include data that originated earlier. *//* 
This dataset updates some but not all of the the GIS layers included in the Albemarle County 2007 Datastack.
*//* ISO Thematic Topics Categories include: boundaries, elevation, environment, location, planning Cadastre, structure, society and transportation. *//*  Datasets/Layers included in this datastack (with non-exclusive list of included attributes): * County boundary 
* Scottsville boundary 
* Comprehensive Planning Areas 
* Comprehensive Plan Landuse - incl. landuse categories: community service, industrial service, institutional, neighborhood density, neighborhood service,  office service, office/regional service, parks and greenways, regional service, town center, transitional, urban density, rural area, special development area, town of Scottsville, Crozet master plan. 
* Crozet Master Plan - current land use, conceptual roads, walkability circles, potential library, and potential school
* Pantops Master Plan - current landuse
* Zoning - incl. rural areas, R1/R2/R4/R6/R10/R15/village residential, planned unit/residential/ mixed_commercial/shopping_center/industrial_park development, neighborhood model district, Monticello historic district, regular/office/highway commercial, light/heavy industry, natural resource extraction overlay, town of Scottsville 
* Areas covered by Proffers from developers 
* Subdivisions 
* Albemarle County Service Authority (ACSA) Jurisdictional Areas - incl. various levels of water/sewer service (0 = no service, 1 = water only, 2 = water and sewer, 3 = water only to existing structures, 4 = limited service, 6 = city sewer and water) 
* Hydrants
* Parcels (annually for 2007-2009, plus current [Aug 2010]) - incl. owner, use code, and description 
* Taxmap index grid
* County-owned parcels (incl. property type) 
* Conservation easements 
* Open Space Use Agreements
* Agricultural and Forest Districts (voluntary landowners program in which land is kept intact) 
* Buildings 
* Road centerlines and edges
* Roadway Improvements
* Bridges 
* Driveways 
* Railroads incl. edges (lines and polys) and bridges 
* Entrance Corridors and overlays 
* Contour lines from 2007 VBMP data (4 ft. interval (county-wide) divided into 23 tiles) plus Digital Terrain Map (DTM) index grid 
* Countywide Critical Slopes (2007 and current)
* Survey Monuments - incl. monument type, elevation, descriptive location 
* Hydrography: lakes, rivers, reservoirs, ponds, streams 
* Watersheds 
* 100 and 500 year floodplains 
* Floodway 
* Water Protection Ordinance Buffers 
* Scenic Streams Overlay 
* School Locations and Parcels 
* School Districts for elementary, middle, and high schools 
* Police stations 
* Police beats (sectors) for county and UVA 
* Fire and Rescue stations and response zones 
* Magisterial districts - incl. population 
* Voting precincts (2003) and Polling places (current) 
* County Parks 
* Shenandoah National Park 
* Ragged Mountain natural area 
* Athletic fields  
 *//* 
Additional 2009 landcover data in raster format is available from the Rivanna River Basin Commission (RRBC) and can be accessed through the County's GIS portal or in person at the Scholars' Lab.  
 *//* Additional data include an Albemarle land records database (zipped) - incl. geocoding information, street and address names, owner, lot size, zoning, assessments, as well as various ArcGIS .LYR legend files for aid in displaying the data. 
 *//* These data were made available to the University of Virginia for educational and research uses only. Access is restricted to students, faculty and staff of the University of Virginia.
*//*  *//*  
SPECIAL SLAB NOTE: 
These datasets reside on the NEW SLAB SHARED DRIVE, and have been uploaded into PostGIS.  Namespace and Datastore folders have been created in GeoServer and Pointsman, but the individual webservices have NOT yet been created (and therefore the links to the "layers" below will not work!!!).</field>
    <field name="dc_rights_s">Public</field>
    <field name="dct_provenance_s">UVa</field>
    <field name="dct_references_s">
                    {
                        "http://schema.org/url": "3f2f9cba-a35d-47de-b027-cd498383f8e8-28",
                        "http://schema.org/thumbnailUrl": "http://gis.lib.virginia.edu:8080/geoserver/wms/reflect?layers=Albemarle2010:ALB10_Floodplain_500y&amp;format=image/jpeg",
                        "http://schema.org/DownloadAction": "http://gis.lib.virginia.edu:8080/geoserver/wfs/reflect?layers=Albemarle2010:ALB10_Floodplain_500y&amp;outputFormat=shape-zip",
                        "http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3": "foobar",
                        "http:isotc211.org/schemas/2005/gmd": "3f2f9cba-a35d-47de-b027-cd498383f8e8-28.iso19139",
                        "http://www.opengis.net/def/serviceType/ogc/wms": "http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wms",
                        "http://www.opengis.net/def/serviceType/ogc/wfs": "http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wfs",
                        "http://www.opengis.net/def/serviceType/ogc/wcs": "http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wcs"
                    }
                </field>
    <field name="layer_id_s">Albemarle2010:ALB10_Floodplain_500y</field>
    <field name="layer_slug_s">uva-Albemarle2010:ALB10_Floodplain_500y</field>
    <field name="layer_geom_type_s">Polygon</field>
    <field name="layer_modified_dt">2010-11-08T17:13:30Z</field>
    <field name="dc_format_s">Shapefile </field>
    <field name="dc_language_s">eng</field>
    <field name="dc_type_s">Dataset</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">boundaries</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">elevation</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">environment</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">location</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">planningCadastre</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">structure</field>
    <field name="dc_subject_sm">transportation</field>
    <field name="dct_issued_s">2010</field>
    <field name="georss_box_s">37.72255 -78.83913 38.27794 -78.20801</field>
    <field name="georss_polygon_s">37.72255 -78.83913 37.72255 -78.20801 38.27794 -78.20801 38.27794 -78.83913 37.72255 -78.83913</field>
    <field name="solr_geom">ENVELOPE(-78.83913, -78.20801, 38.27794, -78.20801)</field>
    <field name="solr_bbox">-78.83913 37.72255 -78.20801 38.27794</field>
    <field name="solr_sw_pt">37.72255,-78.83913</field>
    <field name="solr_ne_pt">38.27794,-78.20801</field>
    <field name="solr_year_i">2014</field>
    <field name="solr_wms_url">http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wms</field>
    <field name="solr_wfs_url">http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wfs</field>
    <field name="solr_wcs_url">http://gis.lib.virginia.edu/geoserver/wcs</field>
  </doc>
</add>
